Guide to the Marilyn Skolnick Papers, 1952-2009 AIS.2001.01
ULS Archives & Special Collections
- Environmental Issues, 1970-2002; I.
  - General Environment, 1986-2002; 12.
    - Clean Water Action, 1998 (Box 14, Folder 19)
    - Clean Water Action, Neville Island, 1997 (Box 14, Folder 20)
    - Commission for Environmental Cooperation, 1997 (Box 14, Folder 21)
    - Commonwealth of Pennsylvania, 1993 (Box 14, Folder 22)
    - Commonwealth of Pennsylvania, 1996-1999 (Box 14, Folder 23)
    - Commonwealth of Pennsylvania, Department of Health, 1996 (Box 14, Folder 24)
    - Community Training and Assistance Center, Request for Proposal, 1995 (Box 14, Folder 25)
    - Conferences, Congresses, Workshops, 1998 (Box 14, Folder 26)
    - Conservation Foundation Letter, 1987-1989 (Box 14, Folder 27)
    - Consumer Product Safety Network, 1987-1989 (Box 14, Folder 28)
    - D'Ella, Evelyn S., undated (Box 14, Folder 29)
    - Data Advisory Committee, 1996 (Box 14, Folder 30)
    - Delaware Valley Regional Planning Commission, 1996 (Box 14, Folder 31)
    - Delaware Valley Regional Planning Commission, 1997-1999 (Box 14, Folder 32)
    - Delaware Valley Regional Planning Commission, 1998 (Box 14, Folder 33)
    - Department of Environmental Protection, 1992 (Box 14, Folder 34)
    - Department of Environmental Protection, Mobile Analytical Services, undated (Box 14, Folder 35)
    - Department of Environmental Resources, undated (Box 14, Folder 36)
    - Department of Environmental Resources, Governor's Waste Minimization Awards, 1993 (Box 14, Folder 37)
    - Department of Environmental Resources, Pollution Prevention P2 Forum, 1994 (Box 14, Folder 38)
    - Department of Environmental Resources, Regulatory Report, 1994 (Box 14, Folder 39)
    - Department of Transportation Correspondence, 1993 (Box 14, Folder 40)
    - Downtown Parking Inventory, Department of City Planning, 1990-1993 (Box 14, Folder 41)
    - Earth Day, 1990 (Box 14, Folder 42)
    - Environment, undated (Box 14, Folder 43)
    - Environment and Health, 1994-1995 (Box 14, Folder 44)
    - Environmental Audits Task Force, Final Reports, undated (Box 14, Folder 45)
    - Environmental Defense Fund, 1988-1989 (Box 14, Folder 46)
    - Environmental Defense Fund, 1994 (Box 14, Folder 47)
    - Environmental Defense Fund, 1995 (Box 14, Folder 48)
    - Environmental Defense Fund, Legal Challenges, 1992-1994 (Box 14, Folder 49)
    - Environmental Defense Fund, Pennsylvania, Vol. 1 No. 1, 1993 (Box 14, Folder 50)
    - Environmental Groups, undated (Box 14, Folder 51)
    - Environmental Law Institute, 1994 (Box 14, Folder 52)
    - Environmental Newsletters, 1993-1997 (Box 14, Folder 53)
    - Environmental Notes, undated (Box 14, Folder 54)
    - Environmental Quality Board, Proposed Rulemaking Plan, 1993 (Box 14, Folder 55)
    - European Community, 1993 (Box 14, Folder 56)
    - Green Newsletter, Vol 1. No. 6, 1991 (Box 14, Folder 57)
    - Gypsy Moth Forum, 1990 (Box 14, Folder 58)
    - Health Department, 1995 (Box 14, Folder 59)
    - Heinz Endowments, Creating Strategic Solutions for Southwestern PA, 1998 (Box 14, Folder 60)
    - ISRC Conference Schedule, 1996 (Box 14, Folder 61)
    - International, 1989-1990 (Box 14, Folder 62)
    - Journals, 1992-1995 (Box 14, Folder 63)
    - Journals, 1993 (Box 14, Folder 64)
    - Journals, 1995-1999 (Box 14, Folder 65)
    - League of Conservation Voters, 1997 (Box 14, Folder 66)
    - League of Conservation Voters, Environmental Voting Chart, 1997-1998 (Box 14, Folder 67)
    - Liberty Borough Non-Attainment, PM-10, 1993-1995 (Box 15, Folder 1)
    - Lincoln Institute, undated (Box 15, Folder 2)
    - Long Range Plan Implementation, Policy Issues, 1994 (Box 15, Folder 3)
    - Monroeville, 1997-1998 (Box 15, Folder 4)
    - Monzo, Al, 1989 (Box 15, Folder 5)
    - National Institute for the Environment, 1995 (Box 15, Folder 6)
    - National Resources Defense Council, 1996 (Box 15, Folder 7)
    - National Resources Defense Council, Premature Mortality, 1996 (Box 15, Folder 8)
    - Natural Resources Defense Council, 1992-1993 (Box 15, Folder 9)
    - Natural Hazards Observer, 1994-2002 (Box 15, Folder 10)
    - Negotiated Environmental Rulemaking, undated (Box 15, Folder 11)
    - Newsletters, 1992-1996 (Box 15, Folder 12)
    - Newsletters, 1996 (Box 15, Folder 13)
    - Newsletters, 1995 (Box 15, Folder 14)
    - Newsletters, 1998 (Box 15, Folder 15)
    - Nine Mile Run, 1999 (Box 15, Folder 16)
    - One Earth, Many Nations, undated (Box 15, Folder 17)
    - Papers, Pittsburgh, undated (Box 15, Folder 18)
    - Pennsylvania, Environmental, 1985-1989 (Box 15, Folder 19)
    - Pennsylvania Environmental Council, 1991 (Box 15, Folder 20)
    - Pennsylvania Environmental Council, List, 1993 (Box 15, Folder 21)
    - Pennsylvania Environmental Network, 1992-1999 (Box 15, Folder 22)
    - Pennsylvania Environmental Network, 1993 (Box 15, Folder 23)
    - Pennsylvania Environmental Network, 1994-1995 (Box 15, Folder 24)
    - Pennsylvania Environmental Network, 2002 (Box 15, Folder 25)
    - Pennsylvania Environmental Network, Newsletter, 1996 (Box 15, Folder 26)
    - Pennsylvania Department of Conservation and Natural Resources, undated (Box 15, Folder 27)
    - Pennsylvania Industrial Development Authority, undated (Box 15, Folder 28)
    - Pennsylvania League of Conservation Voters, Environmental Scorecard, 2000 (Box 15, Folder 29)
    - Pittsburgh, 1986-1987 (Box 15, Folder 30)
    - Pittsburgh, 1993 (Box 15, Folder 31)
    - Pittsburgh High Technology Council, undated (Box 15, Folder 32)
    - Pittsburgh Technology Council, 1999 (Box 15, Folder 33)
    - Planning Updates, 1999-2000 (Box 15, Folder 34)
    - Public Citizen, 1998 (Box 15, Folder 36)
    - Public Affairs Comment, 1988 (Box 15, Folder 35)
    - Public Involvement Docket Comments, undated (Box 15, Folder 37)
    - Regional Marketing Coalition, undated (Box 15, Folder 38)
    - Reports, Public Welfare, 1997 (Box 15, Folder 39)
    - Research, Court Cases, 1996 (Box 15, Folder 40)
    - SBO/SBAP National Conference, 1999 (Box 15, Folder 41)
    - SWPA Growth Alliance, 1994-1995 (Box 15, Folder 42)
    - Southwest Research and Information Center, 1993 (Box 15, Folder 43)
    - SWPRDC, Overall Economic Development Plan, 1994 (Box 15, Folder 44)
    - Steering Committee, 1996 (Box 15, Folder 45)
    - Student Environmental Action Coalition, 1999 (Box 15, Folder 46)
    - Three Rivers Art Festival, 1986 (Box 15, Folder 47)
    - Timbering, 2000 (Box 15, Folder 48)
    - Transportation Research Board, Environmental Justice Subcommittees, 1997 (Box 15, Folder 49)
    - Tri-State Environmental Newsletter, 1993 (Box 15, Folder 50)
    - Tribune Review Commentary, 1998 (Box 15, Folder 51)
    - United States of America and Allegheny County versus Shenango Incorporated, 1999 (Box 15, Folder 52)
    - U.S. Department of Agriculture, undated (Box 15, Folder 53)
  - Global Warming, 1993-1994; 13.
    The documents in this subseries date from 19933-1994 and are arranged by year.
    - 1993 (Box 15, Folder 54)
    - 1994 (Box 15, Folder 55)
  - Growth Management, 1993; 14.
    The materials in the Growth Management subseries date from 1993 and are arranged by year.
    - 1993 (Box 15, Folder 56)
  - Hazardous Materials, 1983-2001; 15.
    The documents in this subseries date from 1983 to 2001 and are arranged alphabetically by subject.
    - Act 101, Municipal Waste Planning, Annual Report, 1991-1992 (Box 15, Folder 57)
    - Agency for Toxic Substances and Disease, Registry, 1996 (Box 15, Folder 58)
    - Bureau of Waste Management, 1988-1989 (Box 15, Folder 59)
    - Center for Hazardous Material Research, undated (Box 15, Folder 60)
    - Center for Hazardous Materials Research, VIP2, 1995 (Box 15, Folder 61)
    - Cytemp Specialty Steel Division, Response Plan, 1989 (Box 15, Folder 62)
    - Environmental, 1992-1997 (Box 15, Folder 63)
    - Environmental Protection Agency, Waste Technologies Industries, 1994 (Box 15, Folder 64)
    - Environmental Synopsis, 1986-1989 (Box 15, Folder 65)
    - Group Incineration, Solid Waste, 1988-1989 (Box 16, Folder 1)
    - Hazardous Household Waste, undated (Box 16, Folder 2)
    - Hazardous Materials, 1995-2000 (Box 16, Folder 3)
    - Hazardous Waste, 1985 (Box 16, Folder 4)
    - Hazardous Waste, 1990-1999 (Box 16, Folder 5)
    - Hazardous Waste, 1991-1992 (Box 16, Folder 6)
    - Hazardous Waste, 1992-1994 (Box 16, Folder 7)
    - Hazardous Waste, 1995 (Box 16, Folder 8)
    - Hazardous Waste, 1995-2001 (Box 16, Folder 9)
    - Hazardous Waste, 1996-1999 (Box 16, Folder 10)
    - Hazardous Waste, 2000 (Box 16, Folder 11)
    - Hazardous Waste, undated (Box 16, Folder 12)
    - Hazardous Waste Facilities, 1992 (Box 16, Folder 13)
    - Hospital Waste, 1991 (Box 16, Folder 14)
    - Incineration, 1986 (Box 16, Folder 15)
    - INMETCO, 1993 (Box 16, Folder 16)
    - Low Level Nuclear, 1994 (Box 16, Folder 17)
    - Low Level Radio-Active, 1986-1987 (Box 16, Folder 18)
    - Low Level Radio-Active Waste, 1989-1990 (Box 16, Folder 19)
    - Low Level Radio-Active Waste Management Program, 1988-1994 (Box 16, Folder 20)
    - Municipal Waste Management, Allegheny County, 1990-1992 (Box 16, Folder 21)
    - North East Allegheny Response Association, Hazardous Materials Response Fund, 1994 (Box 16, Folder 22)
    - Nuclear, 1995 (Box 16, Folder 23)
    - Nuclear Waste, 1995 (Box 16, Folder 24)
    - Rachel's Hazardous Waste News, 1988-1989 (Box 16, Folder 25)
    - Radiation, 1990 (Box 16, Folder 26)
    - RWC Waste Paper, 1986-1989 (Box 16, Folder 27)
    - Residual Waste, 1990 (Box 16, Folder 28)
    - Right to Know, 1983 (Box 16, Folder 29)
    - Solid Waste, Act 97, 1988 (Box 16, Folder 30)
    - Three Mile Island, 1993 (Box 16, Folder 31)
    - Toxic Cleanup, 1990 (Box 16, Folder 32)
    - Toxic Waste, 1988 (Box 16, Folder 33)
    - Toxins, 1992-1998 (Box 16, Folder 34)
    - T.R.A.S.H., 1986 (Box 16, Folder 35)
    - Waste, 1989 (Box 16, Folder 36)
    - Waste, 1995 (Box 16, Folder 37)
    - Waste, 1995-1997 (Box 16, Folder 38)
    - Waste Not, 1988 (Box 16, Folder 39)
    - Waste Not, 1988-1989 (Box 16, Folder 40)
    - Waste Not, 1990-1991 (Box 16, Folder 41)
    - Waste Not, 1991-1994 (Box 16, Folder 42)
  - Land Use, 1970-2002; 16.
    The documents in the Land Use subseries date from 1970 to 2002 and are arranged alphabetically by subject.
    - 1990-1993 (Box 16, Folder 43)
    - 1991-2001 (Box 16, Folder 44)
    - 1992-1998 (Box 16, Folder 45)
    - 1994 (Box 16, Folder 46-47)
    - 1994-1995 (Box 17, Folder 1)
    - 1994-1998 (Box 17, Folder 2)
    - 1994-2000 (Box 17, Folder 3)
    - 1995-1997 (Box 17, Folder 4)
    - 1996-2001 (Box 17, Folder 5)
    - 1997 (Box 17, Folder 6)
    - 1998 (Box 17, Folder 7)
    - 2000 (Box 17, Folder 8)
    - 2000-2001 (Box 17, Folder 9)
    - 10000 Friends of PA, Municipal Planning Code, undated (Box 17, Folder 10)
    - A Profile of Change, A-B, 1970-1980 (Box 17, Folder 11)
    - A Profile of Change, C-H, 1970-1980 (Box 17, Folder 12)
    - A Profile of Change, K-O, 1970-1980 (Box 17, Folder 13)
    - A Profile of Change, P-W, 1970-1980 (Box 17, Folder 14)
    - Agriculture, 1995-1996 (Box 17, Folder 15)
    - Allegheny County, 2000 (Box 17, Folder 16)
    - Allegheny County Environmental Issues, 1993-1995 (Box 17, Folder 17)
    - Allegheny Defense Project, 2001 (Box 17, Folder 18)
    - Allegheny County Library Association, 1996 (Box 17, Folder 19)
    - Allegheny County Natural Heritage Inventory, 1994 (Box 17, Folder 20)
    - Allegheny County Trail Alliance (Box 17, Folder 21)
    - Baker Environmental Inc, Designs, undated (Box 17, Folder 22)
    - City of Pittsburgh, Department of City Planning, 1999 (Box 17, Folder 23)
    - City of Pittsburgh, Department of Conservation and Natural Resources, 1996 (Box 17, Folder 24)
    - Central Appalachian Eco-region Task Force, 1993 (Box 17, Folder 25)
    - Correspondence, 1999-2000 (Box 17, Folder 26)
    - Department of Conservation and Natural Resources, Bureau of State Parks, undated (Box 17, Folder 27)
    - DER Roundtable, 1990 (Box 17, Folder 28)
    - Delaware Valley Regional Planning Commission, 1998 (Box 17, Folder 29)
    - Environment, 1995-1999 (Box 17, Folder 30)
    - Environmental Protection and Natural Resources, Update, 1995 (Box 17, Folder 31)
    - Erosion and Sediment, 1988 (Box 17, Folder 32)
    - House Bill No. 1613, 1614, 1615, Skolnick Transcriptions, 1997 (Box 17, Folder 33)
    - Lancaster County Comprehensive Plan, Growth Management, 1993 (Box 17, Folder 34)
    - Lancaster County New Comprehensive Plan, Update 1-7, 1997 (Box 17, Folder 35)
    - Legislation, 1995-1996 (Box 17, Folder 36)
    - Marilyn Skolnick, 1991 (Box 17, Folder 37)
    - Mexico, 1993 (Box 17, Folder 38)
    - Montaur Trail, 1992 (Box 17, Folder 39)
    - National Land Use, 1990-1995 (Box 17, Folder 40)
    - National Land Use, 1994-2001 (Box 17, Folder 41)
    - National Land Use, 1998 (Box 17, Folder 42)
    - National Land Use, 1998 (Box 18, Folder 1)
    - National Parks, undated (Box 18, Folder 2)
    - Natural Resources, 2000 (Box 18, Folder 3)
    - Neighborhoods for Living Roster, 1990 (Box 18, Folder 4)
    - Open Space, 1993-1998 (Box 18, Folder 5)
    - Open Space, 1998-1999 (Box 18, Folder 6)
    - Parks, 1994 (Box 18, Folder 7)
    - Pennsylvania Land Use, 1995 (Box 18, Folder 8)
    - Pennsylvania Land Use, 1999 (Box 18, Folder 9)
    - Pennsylvania Land Use, 2000 (Box 18, Folder 10)
    - Pennsylvania Land Use, 1999-2002 (Box 18, Folder 11)
    - Pittsburgh Downtown Plan, 1996-1997 (Box 18, Folder 12-14)
    - Pittsburgh Urban Zoning Code, 1993 (Box 18, Folder 15)
    - Pittsburgh Urban Zoning Code, undated (Box 18, Folder 16)
    - Revitalization of the Greater Pittsburgh Region, 1994 (Box 18, Folder 17)
    - Rails to Trails, 1997 (Box 18, Folder 18)
    - Rails to Trails, Testimony, Marianne Wesley Fawler, 1997 (Box 18, Folder 19)
    - Senate Bill No. 270, 1998 (Box 18, Folder 20)
    - Transportation Research Board, 1997 (Box 18, Folder 21)
    - Water, 1997-1999 (Box 18, Folder 22)
    - Zoning, 1986 (Box 18, Folder 23)
    - Zoning, 1987 (Box 18, Folder 24)
    - Zoning, 1997 (Box 18, Folder 25-27)
    - Zoning, 1998 (Box 18, Folder 28)
  - Newsclippings, 1982-1998; 17.
    The materials in this subseries date from 1982 to 1998 and are arranged by year.
    - 1982-1992 (Box 18, Folder 29)
    - 1984-1988 (Box 18, Folder 30)
    - 1985 (Box 18, Folder 31-32)
    - 1987 (Box 18, Folder 33-34)
    - 1988-1990 (Box 18, Folder 35)
    - 1989 (Box 18, Folder 36)
    - 1989-1991 (Box 19, Folder 1)
    - 1993-1994 (Box 19, Folder 2-3)
    - 1994-1996 (Box 19, Folder 4)
    - 1994-1999 (Box 19, Folder 5)
    - 1995-1996 (Box 19, Folder 6-7)
    - 1995-2000 (Box 19, Folder 8)
    - 1996 (Box 19, Folder 9-10)
    - 1997-1998 (Box 19, Folder 11)
  - Pesticides, 1985-1993; 18.
    The documents in this subseries date from 1985 to 1993 and are arranged year and subject.
    - 1989 (Box 19, Folder 12)
    - 1993 (Box 19, Folder 13)
    - undated (Box 19, Folder 14)
    - Pennsylvania Spraying Policy, 1985 (Box 19, Folder 15)
  - Pollution, 1974-2001; 19.
    The materials in the Pollution subseries date from 1974 to 2001 and are arranged alphabetically by subject.
    - 1976-1991 (Box 19, Folder 16)
    - 1989-1995 (Box 19, Folder 17)
    - 1991 (Box 19, Folder 18)
    - 1991-1995 (Box 19, Folder 19)
    - 1993-1999 (Box 19, Folder 20)
    - 1994 (Box 19, Folder 21-23)
    - 1994-1996 (Box 19, Folder 24)
    - 1995 (Box 19, Folder 25)
    - 1995-1997 (Box 19, Folder 26)
    - 1996 (Box 19, Folder 27)
    - 1996-2001 (Box 19, Folder 28)
    - 1997-1998 (Box 19, Folder 29)
    - 1998 (Box 19, Folder 30-31)
    - 1998-2001 (Box 19, Folder 32)
    - 2001 (Box 19, Folder 33-34)
    - Air Pollution, Facts, 1997-1998 (Box 19, Folder 35)
    - Air Pollution, Pennsylvania General Assembly Conservation Committee, 1995 (Box 19, Folder 36)
    - Air Pollution, Prevention Articles, 1996 (Box 19, Folder 37)
    - Air Pollution, VOC Control Requirement, 1988 (Box 19, Folder 38)
    - Air Quality, 1991-1993 (Box 19, Folder 39)
    - Allegheny County Health Department, 1993-1996 (Box 20, Folder 1)
    - ACHD, 1996-1998 (Box 20, Folder 2)
    - ACHD, 1997-2001 (Box 20, Folder 3)
    - ACHD, 1998-2001 (Box 20, Folder 4)
    - ACHD, 1999-2000 (Box 20, Folder 5)
    - ACHD, Air Pollution, 1988-1997 (Box 20, Folder 6)
    - ACHD, Air Pollution, 1989-1990 (Box 20, Folder 7)
    - ACHD, Air Pollution, 1998 (Box 20, Folder 8)
    - ACHD, Air Monitoring Subcommittee, 1993-1994 (Box 20, Folder 9)
    - ACHD, Air Pollution Control Advisory Committee, 1987 (Box 20, Folder 10)
    - ACHD, Air Pollution Control Advisory Committee, 1988 (Box 20, Folder 11)
    - ACHD, Air Pollution Control Advisory Committee, 1988-1992 (Box 20, Folder 12)
    - ACHD, Air Pollution Control Advisory Committee, 1989 (Box 20, Folder 13)
    - ACHD, Air Pollution Control Advisory Committee, 1990 (Box 20, Folder 14)
    - ACHD, Air Pollution Control Advisory Committee, 1990-1991 (Box 20, Folder 15)
    - ACHD, Air Pollution Control Advisory Committee, 1990-1998 (Box 20, Folder 16)
    - ACHD, Air Pollution Control Advisory Committee, 1991 (Box 20, Folder 17)
    - ACHD, Air Pollution Control Advisory Committee, 1992-1993 (Box 20, Folder 18)
    - ACHD, Air Pollution Control Advisory Committee, 1995 (Box 20, Folder 19)
    - ACHD, Air Pollution Control Advisory Committee, 1996 (Box 20, Folder 20)
    - ACHD, Air Pollution Control Advisory Committee, 1997 (Box 20, Folder 21)
    - ACHD, Air Pollution Control Advisory Committee, 1997-1998 (Box 20, Folder 22)
    - ACHD, Air Pollution Control Advisory Committee, 1998-1999 (Box 20, Folder 23)
    - ACHD, Air Pollution Control Advisory Committee, 1999 (Box 20, Folder 24)
    - ACHD, Air Pollution Control Advisory Committee, 2000 (Box 20, Folder 25)
    - ACHD, Air Pollution Prevention Subcommittee, 1995 (Box 20, Folder 26)
    - ACHD, Air Pollution Prevention Subcommittee, 1996 (Box 20, Folder 27)
    - ACHD, Air Pollution Prevention Subcommittee, 1997 (Box 20, Folder 28)
    - ACHD, Air Pollution Prevention Subcommittee, 1999 (Box 20, Folder 29)
    - ACHD, Air Pollution Permits, 1995 (Box 20, Folder 30)
    - ACHD, Air Quality, 1987 (Box 20, Folder 31)
    - ACHD, Air Quality, 1988 (Box 20, Folder 32)
    - ACHD, Air Quality, 1989 (Box 20, Folder 33)
    - ACHD, Air Quality Program, 2000 (Box 20, Folder 34)
    - ACHD, Air Toxics Subcommittee, 1987 (Box 21, Folder 1)
    - ACHD, Air Toxics Subcommittee, 1988 (Box 21, Folder 2)
    - ACHD, Air Toxics Subcommittee, 1988-1989 (Box 21, Folder 3)
    - ACHD, Bureau of Air Pollution Control, 1988 (Box 21, Folder 4)
    - ACHD, Bureau of Environmental Control, 1995 (Box 21, Folder 5)
    - ACHD, Criteria Pollutant Subcommittee, 1998 (Box 21, Folder 6)
    - ACHD, Criteria Pollutant Subcommittee, Members, 1997 (Box 21, Folder 7)
    - ACHD, Portion State Implementation Plan, 1988 (Box 21, Folder 8)
    - ACHD, Public Meeting, 1989 (Box 21, Folder 9)
    - ACHD, Regulation Subcommittee, 1994 (Box 21, Folder 10)
    - ACHD, Testimony re: Article XXI Regulations, 1995 (Box 21, Folder 11)
    - American Lung Association, 1996 (Box 21, Folder 12)
    - Asthma, 1995 (Box 21, Folder 13)
    - Department of Environmental Protection, 1995-1998 (Box 21, Folder 14)
    - Department of Environmental Protection, 1998-2000 (Box 21, Folder 15)
    - Department of Environmental Resources, 1992 (Box 21, Folder 16)
    - Emissions, 1974 (Box 21, Folder 17)
    - Emissions, 1995 (Box 21, Folder 18)
    - Emissions, Low, 1993 (Box 21, Folder 19)
    - Emissions, Low, Final Report, 1993 (Box 21, Folder 20)
    - Emissions, Low, American Lung Association Studies, 1993-1999 (Box 21, Folder 21)
    - Emissions, Low, Department of Transportation, undated (Box 21, Folder 22)
    - Environmental, 1994-1996 (Box 21, Folder 23)
    - Environmental, 1999 (Box 21, Folder 24)
    - Environmental, undated (Box 21, Folder 25)
    - Envirotest, 1994 (Box 21, Folder 26)
    - EPA Project Summary, Emission at Landfills, 1986 (Box 21, Folder 27)
    - GASP, 1991 (Box 21, Folder 28)
    - GASP, 1996 (Box 21, Folder 29)
    - GASP, 2001 (Box 21, Folder 30)
    - Kosmos Cement Company, 1985-1991 (Box 21, Folder 31)
    - Kosmos Cement Company, 1991 (Box 21, Folder 32)
    - Kosmos Cement Company, EPA Report, 1991 (Box 21, Folder 33)
    - Kosmos Cement Company, Southdown Environmental Systems Annual Report, 1990 (Box 22, Folder 1)
    - Indoor Air Pollution, 1989 (Box 22, Folder 2)
    - Joint Legislative Air and Water Pollution Control and Conservation Committee, 1999 (Box 22, Folder 3)
    - Ozone, 1995 (Box 22, Folder 4)
    - Ozone, Docket No. A-99-10, 1999 (Box 22, Folder 5)
    - P2 Forum, Pollution Prevention, 1995 (Box 22, Folder 6)
    - Pennsylvania, 1999-2001 (Box 22, Folder 7)
    - Pennsylvania Cleans the Air, 1993 (Box 22, Folder 8)
    - Pennsylvania, Correspondence, 1999 (Box 22, Folder 9)
    - Pennsylvania General Assembly, Environmental Synopsis, 1999 (Box 22, Folder 10)
    - Power Plant, 2000 (Box 22, Folder 11)
    - Prevention, 1993 (Box 22, Folder 12-13)
    - Proposed Changes to Article XXI, 2000 (Box 22, Folder 14)
    - Reports, ACHD Regulation Subcommittee, 1987 (Box 22, Folder 15)
    - Reports, School of Public Health, Particulates, 1995 (Box 22, Folder 16)
    - SMOG, undated (Box 22, Folder 17)
    - Source Reduction, 1994 (Box 22, Folder 18-19)
    - Toxic Resources, 2000 (Box 22, Folder 20)
    - West Virginia Scorecard, 1991 (Box 22, Folder 21)
    - Western Pennsylvania Scorecard, 1993 (Box 22, Folder 22)
    - VIP2, 1996 (Box 22, Folder 23)
    - VIP2 Annual Report, 1998 (Box 22, Folder 24)
  - Recycling, 1987-2000; 20.
    The materials in the Recycling subseries date from 1987 to 2000 and are arranged alphabetically by subject.
    - 3rd Annual Industrial Site Recycling Conference, 1997 (Box 22, Folder 25-26)
    - Allegheny Recycling Corporation, 1988 (Box 22, Folder 27)
    - Department of Environmental Protection, 1996-1998 (Box 22, Folder 28)
    - Department of Environmental Protection, 1997 (Box 22, Folder 29-30)
    - Department of Environmental Protection, 1997-1999 (Box 22, Folder 31)
    - Department of Environmental Protection, 1997-1998 (Box 22, Folder 32)
    - Department of Environmental Protection, Roundtable, 1996 (Box 22, Folder 33)
    - Department of Environmental Resources, undated (Box 22, Folder 34)
    - Industrial Site Recycling Conference, 1997 (Box 22, Folder 35)
    - Miscellaneous, 1987-1989 (Box 22, Folder 36)
    - Miscellaneous, 1988 (Box 22, Folder 37)
    - Miscellaneous, 1995-1998 (Box 22, Folder 38)
    - Miscellaneous, 1997 (Box 22, Folder 39)
    - Miscellaneous, undated (Box 22, Folder 40)
    - Pennsylvania Land Recycling Manual, 1997 (Box 22, Folder 41-42)
    - Pennsylvania Land Recycling Program, Pamphlet, 2000 (Box 22, Folder 43)
    - Recycling Group, Project Pittsburgh, 1989 (Box 22, Folder 44)
    - The Rush to Burn, America's Greatest Gamble, 1988 (Box 22, Folder 45)
    - Waste Management, Recycle America, 1990 (Box 22, Folder 46)
    - Western Pennsylvania Recycling Workshop, 1989 (Box 22, Folder 47)
  - Solar Technology, 1998; 21.
    The documents in this subseries date from 1998 and are arranged by year.
    - Solarex, 1998 (Box 23, Folder 1)
  - Sludge, 1988-1991; 22.
    The documents in the Sludge subseries date from 1988 to 1991 and are arranged by year.
    - 1988-1990 (Box 23, Folder 2)
    - 1990 (Box 23, Folder 3-4)
    - 1989 (Box 23, Folder 5)
    - 1991 (Box 23, Folder 6)
  - SPRAWL, 1980-2001; 23.
    The materials in the SPRAWL subseries date from 1980 to 2001 and are arranged alphabetically by year and then alphabetically by subject.
    - 1980-2001 (Box 23, Folder 7)
    - 1994-1997 (Box 23, Folder 8)
    - 1995 (Box 23, Folder 9)